It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now they return to the Sabahodi Archipelago and move forward to the next stage of their journey, the New World.
It's for a concert today. He's calling himself Soul King.
Yeah, there's a story behind that.
He didn't say anything about this to me, but he's making a lot of people happy with his music.
He might not want to be a player anymore.
Huh? Look, it's that kid with the backpack. Maybe our luck ain't so bad after all.
Oh, it's you guys!
Reporting from Crow 46.
All the new recruits the Straw Hats picked up are gathering here and from the looks of things, I'd say there might be nearly a hundred of them.
There are four captains here at least.
Big guns assembled! The danger of the fake Straw Hats!
The extra Hats!
Thank you, thank you everybody.
All right, the wall.
45 degrees!
Thank you for coming out!
Now that is what I'm talking about.
Nice work, sir.
Hell yeah.
Oh, I'm like a rock star, baby.
Sinking down to my bones.
This is Grove number 46 with an update.
The pirates keep pouring in.
There's definitely over a hundred now.
None of the main straw hats are here yet, but even so, I would approach with extreme caution.
Hey, what's wrong?
Did they find you?
This is bad.
Tell the backup they need to hurry.
Well now, what have we here?
Who is this little fellow whispering behind the rock because he looks like a navy soldier?
And my goodness, what is this?
You weren't looking to crash our harmless party, were you?
No!
That's not very civil at all!
Because if you were calling your friends for backup, that would not end well, seeing as
they weren't invited.
Show some manners.
I saw him.
He was calling.
No!
I was going to call them, but I hadn't gotten through them just yet.
That is good to hear.
And I say that for your sake, too.
Because if your friends did show up, this Grove would be covered in blood.
Their blood.
And your blood.
Come on, Koraboo.
Back me up here.
Huh?
I wasn't listening.
I'm sorry.
Who do you think you're bowing to, moron?
I'm over here.
Please, forgive me.
You still can't get it right.
What, are you blind or just stupid?
He's famous for killing marines.
Huh?
Hmm.
do you think this is a joke he really stabbed that guy then the stories are
true god have mercy he is but a fool he grabbed his gun this poor misguided soul trying to incite
violence against me in your infinite kindness please show him mercy sorry gods sorry very sorry
sorry gods now brother bury him bury this sinful transgressor alive dig so that his poor soul may
be free roger wait a second what if i call them and tell them not to come that would be good right
that's enough caribou you can bury that nobody later we got bigger fists to fry right now
just tell us what you want from us captain loopy we're ready to go
take a look around you boys this is history in the making you probably don't know each
other yet but you'll be titus brothers soon enough from here on out your straw hats
not a bad deal and i swear when i become king of the pirates you're gonna know you made the right call
yeah but i need a promise from you first because a real king needs loyal subjects ones that will
live and die for him and wait on him hand and fight anything you say you're the man who escaped impel
down wrecked any's lobby stormed marine ford and fought the admirals you've got the world government
quaking in its boots sailing the seas with you is like a trade come true listen there's only one man
fit to be king of the pirates and he's standing right there you get with him or you get left in
the dust looks like the king's all here is this it so where is everyone stop making me wait
all right enough
i didn't call you here at a party we got business to attend to some jackasses out there haven't been
showing me the respect i deserve that is to say they insulted my aunt
a red-haired girl a long-nosed guy and a brat with a backpack find him and bring him to me the
bastards are still in the archipelago somewhere consider it done boss we'll make him suffer you'll
see i gotta say though people sure can change a lot in two years for one you guys hardly talk at all
anymore he's more dangerous than we thought we gotta get him to the boss pronto or he's gonna rat us out
to everyone who is this guy i don't know but in the meantime let's try not to talk so he doesn't catch on
the captain's right there he could figure this out on his own sounds like a plan i don't know what
happened but it seems like you're getting along a lot better too yep time changes lots of stuff
like your faces i mean unless you're wearing a disguise like me
the navy is here so they know
oh very well then take it easy no pushing
i still need a moment more my fans are calling for an encore you see and i can't let them down
i think i owe them this much at least so please wait up for me
those cheers could bring a dead man back from his grave baby
now listen friends i'm afraid that i've got something a bit heavy to share with you today
after this show i
this is the navy nobody move what's the deal that's not cool this is the last living member of the rumbar
pirates the humming swordsman brooke presumed dead until now with a bounty of 33 million despite his
skeletal state our reports indicate that soul king is this pirate in addition to his previous crimes
we have further information that indicates he is now working for straw hat luffy
soul king brooke or rather humming swordsman brooke you're under arrest for piracy
no it can't be true i feel like my whole life is alive he was a pirate all along but wait straw hat
luffy's been missing for years now it's been a good run brooke but it's over your betrayal's not
exactly a surprise mr manager you're the one to blame telling me you were gonna retire right after
the show how could you do this to me a pity but it seems like i would have been better off keeping you
in that cage after all we were gonna be rich but now our company's ruined you're nothing but a filthy
traitor if my life's going to hell i'm taking you with me
so
that is so cool heck yeah can i get a body like that too
that too
so can you like transforming stuff shoot beams missiles laser eyes hurry show me shall we
i can hear the dreams of men on my massive metal shoulders wow i'm back and better than ever
i'm not just me
one thing's bugging me though those giant robo hands are great for bashing but how are you supposed to
do detail work never doubt the master wow he looks terrible did he do that to himself
it's frankie don't ask whoa this must be the coating huh wanna see something else cool press my nose
your nose press and hold it for three seconds or more apply pressure to the nasal region human
holy crap he's like a real robot excited one two three wow he grew hair
wait a second can you style it easy as pie hey look who it is what's up yeah i see you
oh like our crew didn't stick out enough already can i see your new weapons please can i
sorry buddy that's the main event so we gotta wait till the captain shows up
mecca he made robot noises is mecca his new catchphrase hello there hey rayleigh hey shocky
sorry to interrupt your reunion but we've kind of got an incident actually two very large incidents
that demand your attention put the guitar down now hands in the air pirate there's no escape
members of the band my lovely chorus this will be my final song will you share it with me
have no fear my music has more than just soul it has true power are you insane you think anyone's
gonna let you play another song you might not see it this way but i'm grateful for the time we spent
together thank you for these past two years and thank you for bringing me here my crew and i have rather
tragic memories of this place we lost an important battle here last time but we're ready to start anew
i'm the musician of the crew i may possess some strength as a swordsman but my job is to make our
journey more fun i've heard the stories they think people are foolish enough to believe that straw hat is
dead will you listen to me he's not straw hat luffy is out there alive and kicking you can tell the world
and while you're at it tell them he's going to be the king of the pirates someday too boy have
i got some news for you guys we better print this one in a jiffy yeah baby he's coming back soon and
when he sets sail i want to send him off soul king style that's so cool do you love me down to my bones
i'll dedicate this to my crew to my friends my soul will sing to you one last time
luffy let's go to the new world together the show is over i said you're under arrest would you shut up
it's his last song let us hear it please what harm could it do she's right you can wait till the show
is over you bastards music is power music is always on your side
one two three four
i call this one new world
some people may call my friend a weirdo
it may be true that he stopped it from zero
but even though he doesn't want the straight and narrow
he's got a heart of gold just like a hero
so
men like him can't help themselves from dreaming
he gazes towards tomorrow eyes are gleaming
but every day a dreamer fights against reality it seems a struggle to be free
if i were alone i might surrender
weight's too heavy for me
when i hear him say it even i can't believe
today is the day we'll bury all our sorrow time to raise the sails they'll tell our tales through every
tomorrow today is the day we're aiming towards a new dawn all our doubts are gone let's move along
cause it's time to sail away
for the new world
for the new world where our dreams will all come true
the new world
what the
Bunch of oof!
Why did you have to get all sentimental like that?
Now we can't cash it on his bounty!
The Navy?
That's right.
They thought those fake straw hats were the real deal and mobilized their forces.
Pacifistas, too.
I have them wiretapped, so there's no mistaking it.
Anyway, Brook is finishing up his concert, but I gave him a call backstage to let him know what was going on.
He said he'd come after the encore, so it shouldn't be long.
Oh, yeah? Giving up stardom to be a lowly pirate?
Goes without saying, but the man's got a backbone.
All right, Nami. Since you're the navigator, there are a few tricks to operating a coded ship I should pass on to you.
Uh, okay. Sure, let's hear it.
We aren't getting ready to take off, are we? We're still missing half the crew here!
I mean, did Luffy even make it to the archipelago yet?
It's all under control.
Captain!
Huh? I'm kind of in the middle of something, you goons!
But we found a backpack guy you was looking for. That's good, right?
He's a friend of the crew, if you follow. Say hi.
In other words, Luffy arrived earlier this morning.
It's almost time to go.
I gave Sanji a baby transponder snail when he stopped by, so I'll tell him to come back.
You should have Zoro with him, too.
Good. We should hurry, because any moment now, the Navy will be attacking with a sizable force.
Unfortunately, there's no way to contact your captain.
But if you follow this Vivre card, you should be able to hunt him down.
Let's hope the fake straw hats buy you a bit of time.
Grove 42 is on the outskirts, so it's close to the sea.
Take the sunny there and be ready to depart on a moment's notice.
I'm sure you'd like to relax after these two difficult years, but it wasn't meant to be.
The winds of the new world wait for no one.
The straw hats are assembled on the sunny and ready to depart, but their captain is still missing.
As a battle breaks out between the fake straw hats and the Navy, Luffy is drawn into the chaos.
Unable to keep a low profile any longer, he shows the world the strength he acquired in his two years of absence.
On the next, One Piece, the battle is on.
Show them what you got from training.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.